

Muhammad Zaryab

Software Engineer



+90 507 446 70 87

zaryabkhan864@gmail.com

Istanbul/Turkey

LinkedIn

My Website

GitHub

ABOUT ME

Experienced software engineer with a passion for developing innovative programs that expedite the efficiency and effectiveness of organizational success. Well-versed in technology and writing code to create systems that are reliable and user-friendly.

Confident communicator, strategic thinker, and innovative creator to develop software that is customized to meet a company's organizational needs, highlight their core competencies, and further their success.

SKILLS

8 / 10
React
9 / 10
Bootstrap
8 / 10
JavaScript
8/10
Node JS
8 / 10
SQL / PLsql
9 / 10
HTML
9 / 10
CSS
7 / 10
Material UI
Material UI 7 / 10

EDUCATION

Masters In Computer Science (MSCS)

Altınbaş University / Istanbul, Turkey 09-2019-Present

Bachelor's In Computer Science

Hamdard University Karachi, Pakistan 2013-2018

EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer Digitaez (Pakistan, 12/2021 – 05/2022)

- Developed and designed couple of websites and web application such as a POS system.
- Researched best practices to share with fellow software team members.
- Presented to management an end-of-term demonstration on valuable software developments that were in the works.

Service Desk Officer

Tabba Heart Hospital (Pakistan, 09/2017-12/2020)

Supporting hospital ERP "HOPE", understanding and analyzing ERP, addresses the end users queries and support issues. Also identify bugs and report to SKM (Shaukat khanum hospital).

A C A D E M I C I N T E R N S H I P S

Software Engineer

Dubai Islamic bank (Pakistan, 07/2015 – 08/2015)

worked on banking ERP, Creating foams using PLSQL, Oracle database 9i.

Software Engineer

DP World (QICT) (Pakistan, 07/2014 - 09/2014)

Worked on logistics ERP, PLsql and Oracle database 9i.

Web Developer

Excloud Software House (Pakistan, 01/2014-04-2014)

Worked on different websites such as restaurants, blogs, product selling.